<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Musings of Fr3d – Live for the journey not the destination</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Live for the journey not the destination on Musings of Fr3d</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2025 05:00:50 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	  <atom:link href="//localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
      
      
    
    
    <item>
      <title>30 tips for 30 years</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/writing/30_tips_for_30_years/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2025 04:14:30 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//localhost:1313/writing/30_tips_for_30_years/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Seek joy in today, tomorrow&amp;rsquo;s joy will follow&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Three decades is not a lot of time in the grand scheme of the universe.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Don&amp;rsquo;t focus on time lost but time treasured&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s okay to be angry at someone else&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s okay to be happy for someone else&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Money is an object but the object is not money.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Wake up each day and think of one thing you love about yourself. You&amp;rsquo;ll feel better.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Conflict and change are synonymous.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Boundaries are for your mind, body and spirit. Set them accordingly.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The best memories are the ones without expectation of the outcome.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Grieve your losses.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Reflect on your gains.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Pick a flower whenever you can, the earth shared it with you after all.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Trauma is toxic when ignored but trauma teaches when you pay attention.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Wear that crop top!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Don&amp;rsquo;t inflate or devalue others.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Eat the cookies at midnight. They tend to taste better&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Your presence in the present is a present.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The top of the hill looks menacing. Trust me, rolling down it is worse&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Eye contact is appreciated, people have really beautiful eyes.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If your intuition is calming telling you to get GTFO, GTFO!!!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Instead of rest days, just rest.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Don&amp;rsquo;t be afraid to employ an icebreaker. It tends to bring out people&amp;rsquo;s humanity&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A nice cry and a laugh afterwards is some pretty darn good medicine&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Thank the sun and moon a little more. They&amp;rsquo;ve been doing it alot longer than we have.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;For every compliment given to others, give yourself one.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hydrate!!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be your own superhero but NO CAPES!!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tell a joke to a stranger, don&amp;rsquo;t worry they didn&amp;rsquo;t pay for tickets.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Read this list backwards. #1 will resonate a little more.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meditation 8 Jan 2025</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/writing/meditation_20250108/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2025 04:14:30 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//localhost:1313/writing/meditation_20250108/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;p&gt;Fog lands and dampens the surrounding marsh.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Each step is treacherous, soggy soles afoot.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The eyes lie upon the pages from which they view.&lt;/p&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
